Guide to the Jerald Brauer Papers 1925-1999
University of Chicago Library
- Series IX: Writings, 1928-1997
  - Subseries 1: Book Projects and Publishers
    - Brauer Drafts, Protestantism in America, n. d. (Box 130, Folder 9)
    - Brauer Drafts and Correspondence, Protestantism in America, 1953-1970 (Box 130, Folder 10)
    - Brauer Correspondence, Protestantism in America, 1951-1954 (Box 131, Folder 1)
    - History of Religions, Preface, 1959 (Box 131, Folder 2)
    - Book Reviews of Brauer's Work, 1971-1977 (Box 131, Folder 3)
    - University of Chicago Press, 1971-1974 (Box 131, Folder 4)
    - Bill Weaver Memorial, n. d. (Box 131, Folder 5)
    - Brauer, "In God We Trust?" n. d. (Box 131, Folder 6)
    - Clippings, 1955, 1965 (Box 131, Folder 7)
    - "The Editor's Bookshelf" n. d. (Box 131, Folder 8)
    - Book Review, "Types of Puritan Piety" n. d. (Box 131, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous Articles, 1954-1994 (Box 131, Folder 10)
    - Revivalism Drafts, 1981 (Box 131, Folder 11)
    - Book Review by Brauer, 1948 (Box 131, Folder 12)
    - Reviews and Correspondence, The Lively Experiment Continued, 1979-1989 (Box 131, Folder 13)
    - Reviews and Correspondence, 1954-1957 (Box 131, Folder 14)
    - Book Review, Encyclopedia of American Religious History, n. d. (Box 131, Folder 15)
    - Book Reviews, 1969 (Box 131, Folder 16)
    - Dictionary of American Biography, 1973-1974 (Box 131, Folder 17)
    - Article, "It's a Question of Quality," Laity Exchange, n. d. (Box 131, Folder 18)
    - Carlson Publishing Project, 1990 (Box 131, Folder 19)
    - Preface on Tillich, n. d. (Box 131, Folder 20)
    - Handbook of Christian Theology, miscellaneous, 1990 (Box 131, Folder 21)
    - Brauer Offprint, "The Christian College" 1958 (Box 131, Folder 22)
    - Brauer Offprint, "Editor's Preface" n. d. (Box 131, Folder 23)
    - Brauer Offprint, "Changing Perspectives on Religion" n. d. (Box 131, Folder 24)
    - Brauer Offprint, "In Appreciation of Joseph Sittler" 1974 (Box 131, Folder 25)
    - Brauer Offprint, "Church and State" 1965 (Box 131, Folder 26)
    - Brauer Offprint, "Protestantism and Theological Education" n. d. (Box 131, Folder 27)
    - Brauer Offprints, "Religious Perspectives on College Teaching", n. d. (Box 131, Folder 28)
    - Brauer, "Basic Questions for the Christian Scholar" 1963 (Box 131, Folder 29)
  - Subseries 2: Articles and Offprints
    - Notes, n. d. (Box 132, Folder 1)
    - Brauer Articles, 1950s (Box 132, Folder 2)
    - Brauer Articles, 1950s (Box 132, Folder 3)
    - Brauer Articles, 1960s (Box 132, Folder 4)
    - Brauer Articles, 1960s (Box 132, Folder 5)
    - Brauer Articles, 1970s (Box 132, Folder 6)
    - Brauer Articles, 1980s (Box 132, Folder 7)
    - Brauer Articles, 1990s (Box 132, Folder 8)
    - Brauer Articles, n. d. (Box 132, Folder 9)
    - Offprints by Others, 1930s-1950s (Box 132, Folder 10)
    - Brauer Articles and Off-prints, 1950s (Box 133, Folder 1)
    - Brauer Articles and Off-prints, 1950s (Box 133, Folder 2)
    - Brauer Articles and Off-prints, 1960s (Box 133, Folder 3)
    - Brauer Articles and Off-prints, 1960s (Box 133, Folder 4)
    - Brauer Articles and Off-prints, 1970s (Box 133, Folder 5)
    - Articles and Off-prints by Others, n. d. (Box 133, Folder 6)
    - Articles and Off-prints by Others, 1940s (Box 133, Folder 7)
    - Articles and Off-prints by Others, 1927 (Box 133, Folder 8)
    - Off-prints and Articles, 1950s (Box 134, Folder 1)
    - Off-prints and Articles, 1950s (Box 134, Folder 2)
    - Off-prints and Articles, 1950s (Box 134, Folder 3)
    - Off-prints and Articles, 1960s (Box 134, Folder 4)
    - Off-prints and Articles, 1960s (Box 134, Folder 5)
    - Off-prints and Articles, 1960s (Box 134, Folder 6)
    - Off-prints and Articles, 1960s (Box 135, Folder 1)
    - Off-prints and Articles, 1960s (Box 135, Folder 2)
    - Off-prints and Articles, 1960s (Box 135, Folder 3)
    - Off-prints and Articles, 1960s (Box 136, Folder 1)
    - Off-prints and Articles, 1970s (Box 136, Folder 2)
    - Off-prints and Articles, 1970s (Box 136, Folder 3)
    - Off-prints and Articles, 1970s (Box 137, Folder 1)
    - Off-prints and Articles, 1970s (Box 137, Folder 2)
    - Off-prints and Articles, 1980s (Box 137, Folder 3)
    - Articles, 1980s (Box 138, Folder 1)
    - Articles, 1980s (Box 138, Folder 2)
    - Articles, 1990s (Box 138, Folder 3)
    - Off-prints, 1990s (Box 138, Folder 4)
    - Off-prints, 1990s (Box 138, Folder 5)
    - Off-prints, n. d. (Box 138, Folder 6)
    - Articles and Off-prints, 1920-1949 (Box 139, Folder 1)
    - Articles and Off-prints, 1950s (Box 139, Folder 2)
    - Articles and Off-prints, 1970s (Box 139, Folder 3)
    - Articles and Off-prints, 1970s (Box 139, Folder 4)
    - Articles and Off-prints, 1980s (Box 139, Folder 5)
    - Articles and Off-prints, 1990s (Box 139, Folder 6)
    - Articles and Off-prints, n. d. (Box 139, Folder 7)
    - Articles and Off-prints, n. d. (Box 139, Folder 8)
    - Articles and Off-prints, n. d. (Box 140, Folder 1)
    - Articles and Off-prints, n. d. (Box 140, Folder 2)
    - Articles and Off-prints, n. d. (Box 140, Folder 3)
    - Articles and Off-prints, n. d. (Box 140, Folder 4)
    - Articles and Off-prints, n. d. (Box 140, Folder 5)
    - Off-prints, n. d. (Box 140, Folder 6)
    - Seminarian, 1951-1952 (Box 140, Folder 7)
    - Clippings, 1960s (Box 140, Folder 8)
    - Clippings, 1960s (Box 140, Folder 9)
    - Newsletters, 1950-1960s (Box 140, Folder 10)
- Series X: Restricted, 1925-1999
  Series X: Restricted contains four subseries. Subseries 1: Restricted Recent Correspondence is restricted until 2020. Subseries 2: Restricted Financial Records is restricted until 2019. Subseries 3 Restricted Student and Faculty Material contains materials that are indefinitely restricted. Subseries 4: Restricted Audio and Visual Materials contains items that are indefinably restricted due to its physical condition or need for Special Equipment.
  - Subseries 1: Restricted Recent Correspondence
    - I-House Board, 1980 (Box 141, Folder 1)
    - I-House Report, 1981 (Box 141, Folder 2)
    - I-House Venezuelan Friends, 1989 (Box 141, Folder 3)
    - I-House Financial Reports, 1985 (Box 141, Folder 4)
    - I-House Araujo, 1982 (Box 141, Folder 5)
    - I-House, Levi, 1988 (Box 141, Folder 6)
    - I-House, Japan, 1991 (Box 141, Folder 7)
    - I-House, 1990 (Box 141, Folder 8)
    - I-House Board, 1990-1991 (Box 141, Folder 9)
    - I-House, 1980s (Box 141, Folder 10)
    - I-House, 1990s (Box 141, Folder 11)
    - I-House, Kubert, 1974 (Box 142, Folder 1)
    - I-House, Pearson, 1984 (Box 142, Folder 2)
    - I-House, Security Department, 1985 (Box 142, Folder 3)
    - I-House, Correspondence, 1991 (Box 142, Folder 4)
    - I-House Board, Correspondence, 1985 (Box 142, Folder 5)
    - I-House, Board Meeting, 1985 (Box 142, Folder 6)
    - I-House Board, Housing, 1985 (Box 142, Folder 7)
    - I-House Board, 1989 (Box 142, Folder 8)
    - I-House Board, 1989 (Box 142, Folder 9)
    - I-House, 1998 (Box 142, Folder 10)
    - I-House, USA/USSR Conference, 1984-1985 (Box 142, Folder 11)
    - I-House, Alumni, 1985 (Box 142, Folder 12)
    - I-House, Development, 1984-1985 (Box 142, Folder 13)
    - I-House Director, 1984-1985 (Box 142, Folder 14)
    - I-House, Festival of Nations, 1985 (Box 142, Folder 15)
    - I-House, Berkeley, 1984-1985 (Box 142, Folder 16)
    - I-House, Philadelphia, 1983-1988 (Box 142, Folder 17)
    - I-House, 5-Year Program, 1984 (Box 142, Folder 18)
    - I-House Executive Correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 142, Folder 19)
    - I-House, General Service, 1985 (Box 142, Folder 20)
    - I-House, Fellowship, 1984-1985 (Box 142, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence, 1977-1997 (Box 143, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1976-1986 (Box 143, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1959-1978 (Box 143, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, n.d. (Box 143, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1975-1978 (Box 143, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1975 (Box 143, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1982 (Box 143, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1978-1994 (Box 143, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1970-1997 (Box 143, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 1993-1994 (Box 144, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1984 (Box 144, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1977-1983 (Box 144, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1969-1979 (Box 144, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1979-1986 (Box 144, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1973-1977 (Box 144, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1975-1978 (Box 144, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1966-1968 (Box 144, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1980 (Box 144, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 1979-1981 (Box 144, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, 1970-1996 (Box 144, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, 1983-1998 (Box 145, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1970-1996 (Box 145, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1978-1991 (Box 145, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1970-1981 (Box 145, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 145, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1979 (Box 145, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1994-1996 (Box 145, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1977-1980 (Box 145, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1970-1996 (Box 145, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 1970-1998 (Box 145, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, 1969-1996 (Box 146, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1970-1997 (Box 146, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1975-1981 (Box 146, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1978 (Box 146, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1976-1982 (Box 146, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1973-1998 (Box 146, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1965-1997 (Box 146, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1970-1997 (Box 146, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1970 (Box 147, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1973-1980 (Box 147, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1972 (Box 147, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1953-1998 (Box 147, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1979-1998 (Box 147, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1970-1993 (Box 147, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1967-1982 (Box 147, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1976-1989 (Box 147, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1967-1995 (Box 147, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 1965-1990 (Box 148, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1972 (Box 148, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1977-1997 (Box 148, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1969-1981 (Box 148, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1975-1980 (Box 148, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1966-1981 (Box 148, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1970-1997 (Box 148, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1962-1983 (Box 148, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1968-1970 (Box 148, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 1979-1983 (Box 149, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1965-1993 (Box 149, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1975-1998 (Box 149, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1970-1996 (Box 149, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1956-1979 (Box 149, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1957 (Box 149, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1975-1996 (Box 150, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1971-1997 (Box 150, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1970-1978 (Box 150, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1958-1980 (Box 150, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1969-1978 (Box 150, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1977 (Box 150, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1973-1976 (Box 150, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1975 (Box 150, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1970-1995 (Box 150, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 1968-1981 (Box 150, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, 1992 (Box 150, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, 1959-1998 (Box 151, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1980 (Box 151, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1966-1998 (Box 151, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1973-1997 (Box 151, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1983-1998 (Box 151, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1970-1984 (Box 151, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1949-1956 (Box 151, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1964-1978 (Box 152, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1968-1983 (Box 152, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1970-1998 (Box 152, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1962-1999 (Box 152, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1970-1996 (Box 152, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1953-1981 (Box 152, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1972-1998 (Box 152, Folder 7)
  - Subseries 2: Restricted Financial Records
    - Divinity School, Financial Records, 1968-1969 (Box 153, Folder 1)
    - Divinity School, Financial Records, 1968-1969 (Box 153, Folder 2)
    - Divinity School, Financial Records, 1968-1969 (Box 153, Folder 3)
    - Divinity School, Financial Records, 1968-1969 (Box 153, Folder 4)
  - Subseries 3: Restricted Student and Faculty Materials
    - Student Papers, 1950s (Box 154, Folder 1)
    - Student Papers, Revivalism, 1979 (Box 154, Folder 2)
    - Student Papers, Revivalism, 1980s (Box 154, Folder 3)
    - Student Papers, Seminar, 1985 (Box 154, Folder 4)
    - Student Papers, 1980s (Box 154, Folder 5)
    - Student Papers, 1980s (Box 154, Folder 6)
    - Puritanism Papers, 1980a (Box 154, Folder 7)
    - Student Papers, 1990s (Box 155, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous Student Papers, 1971-1980 (Box 155, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous Student Papers, 1951-1985 (Box 155, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous student Papers, 1968-1984 (Box 155, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous Student Papers, 1973-1984 (Box 155, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous Student Papers, 1977-1997 (Box 155, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous Student Papers, 1969-1997 (Box 155, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous Student Papers, 1968-1984 (Box 156, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous Student Papers, 1984-1993 (Box 156, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous Student Papers, 1993 (Box 156, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous Student Papers, 1977-1998 (Box 156, Folder 4)
    - Puritanism, Course Records, 1965-1966 (Box 156, Folder 5)
    - Puritan Revolution Readings, n. d. (Box 156, Folder 6)
    - Puritanism Papers, 1975 (Box 156, Folder 7)
    - Puritanism Papers, 1984 (Box 156, Folder 8)
    - Theocratic Ideal Papers, n.d. (Box 156, Folder 9)
    - Dissertation Proposals, n. d. (Box 156, Folder 10)
    - Seminar Papers, 1960 (Box 156, Folder 11)
    - Seminar Papers, 1960 (Box 157, Folder 1)
    - Seminar Papers, 1960 (Box 157, Folder 2)
    - Seminar Papers, 1960 (Box 157, Folder 3)
    - Seminar Papers, 1960 (Box 157, Folder 4)
    - Student Papers 1965 (Box 157, Folder 5)
    - Student Paper with Notes, 1959 (Box 157, Folder 6)
    - Student Statements for Oral Exams, n. d. (Box 157, Folder 7)
    - Student Statements for Oral Exams, n. d. (Box 157, Folder 8)
    - Student Statements for Oral Exams, n. d. (Box 157, Folder 9)
    - Student Statements for Oral Exams, n. d. (Box 157, Folder 10)
    - Student Statements for Oral Exams, 1958, 1967 (Box 158, Folder 1)
    - Course Grades, 1956 (Box 158, Folder 2)
    - Language Exams (Box 158, Folder 3)
    - Ph. D. Students (Box 158, Folder 4)
    - A.M. Ph.D. Committee Petitions, 1959 (Box 158, Folder 5)
    - A.M. Ph.D. Committee Petitions, 1958 (Box 158, Folder 6)
    - A.M. Ph.D. Committee, 1957-1958 (Box 158, Folder 7)
    - A.M. Ph.D. Committee, 1958 (Box 158, Folder 8)
    - B.D. Students, Correspondence, 1958 (Box 158, Folder 9)
    - Course Grades, 1957 (Box 158, Folder 10)
    - Course Grades, 1956 (Box 158, Folder 11)
    - Course Grades, 1956 (Box 158, Folder 12)
    - Comprehensive Exam Grades, 1956 (Box 158, Folder 13)
    - Course Grades, 1956 (Box 158, Folder 14)
    - Course Grades, 1958 (Box 158, Folder 15)
    - Student Program Cards, n. d. (Box 158, Folder 16)
    - Class Rosters, 1974-1989 (Box 158, Folder 17)
    - Student Rankings, 1992 (Box 158, Folder 18)
    - Grade Reports, 1955-1989 (Box 158, Folder 19)
    - Student Papers and Correspondence, 1977-1996 (Box 158, Folder 20)
    - Academic Reports, n. d. (Box 159, Folder 1)
    - Student Papers, 1978 (Box 159, Folder 2)
    - Student Papers, 1978 (Box 159, Folder 3)
    - Student Papers, n.d. (Box 159, Folder 4)
    - Student Papers, 1968 (Box 159, Folder 5)
    - Student Papers, 1959 (Box 159, Folder 6)
    - Student Papers, n.d. (Box 159, Folder 7)
    - Student Papers, n.d. (Box 159, Folder 8)
    - Student Papers, 1985 (Box 159, Folder 9)
    - Student Papers, n.d. (Box 159, Folder 10)
    - Student Papers, n.d. (Box 159, Folder 11)
    - Student Papers, 1972-1974 (Box 159, Folder 12)
    - Student Papers, n.d. (Box 159, Folder 13)
    - Student Papers, 1982-1983 (Box 159, Folder 14)
    - Student Papers, n.d. (Box 159, Folder 15)
    - Student Papers, 1978 (Box 159, Folder 16)
    - Student Papers, n.d. (Box 159, Folder 17)
    - Student Papers, 1992 (Box 159, Folder 18)
    - Student Papers, n.d. (Box 159, Folder 19)
    - Student Papers, 1992 (Box 159, Folder 20)
    - Student Papers, 1990 (Box 159, Folder 21)
    - Student Papers, n.d. (Box 159, Folder 22)
    - Student Papers, 1991 (Box 159, Folder 23)
    - Student Papers, 1970 (Box 160, Folder 1)
    - Student Papers, 1978 (Box 160, Folder 2)
    - Student Papers, n.d. (Box 160, Folder 3)
    - Student Papers, 1970 (Box 160, Folder 4)
    - Student Papers, 1975 (Box 160, Folder 5)
    - Student Papers, 1965 (Box 160, Folder 6)
    - Student Papers, n.d. (Box 160, Folder 7)
    - Student Papers, 1959 (Box 160, Folder 8)
    - Student Papers, 1970 (Box 160, Folder 9)
    - Student Papers, 1970 (Box 160, Folder 10)
    - Student Papers, 1970 (Box 160, Folder 11)
    - Student Papers, n.d. (Box 160, Folder 12)
    - Student Papers, n.d. (Box 160, Folder 13)
    - Student Papers, 1970 (Box 160, Folder 14)
    - Student Papers, n.d. (Box 160, Folder 15)
    - Student Papers, 1970 (Box 160, Folder 16)
    - Student Papers, 1970 (Box 160, Folder 17)
    - Student Papers, 1970 (Box 160, Folder 18)
    - Student Papers, 1970 (Box 160, Folder 19)
    - Student Papers, 1970 (Box 160, Folder 20)
    - Student Papers, 1970 (Box 160, Folder 21)
    - Student Papers, 1970 (Box 160, Folder 22)
    - Student Papers, 1970 (Box 160, Folder 23)
    - Student Papers, 1973-1976 (Box 160, Folder 24)
    - Student Papers, 1975 (Box 160, Folder 25)
    - Student Papers, 1984-1994 (Box 160, Folder 26)
    - Student Correspondence, 1970-1978 (Box 160, Folder 27)
    - Student Papers, 1973 (Box 161, Folder 1)
    - Student Papers, n.d. (Box 161, Folder 2)
    - Student Papers, 1976 (Box 161, Folder 3)
    - Student Papers, 1976 (Box 161, Folder 4)
    - Student Papers, n.d. (Box 161, Folder 5)
    - Student Papers, n.d. (Box 161, Folder 6)
    - Student Papers, n.d. (Box 161, Folder 7)
    - Student Papers, 1971-1972 (Box 161, Folder 8)
    - Student Papers, n.d. (Box 161, Folder 9)
    - Student Papers, 1976 (Box 161, Folder 10)
    - Student Papers, 1974 (Box 161, Folder 11)
    - Student Papers, n.d. (Box 162, Folder 1)
    - Student Papers, 1991 (Box 162, Folder 2)
    - Student Papers, 1989-1990 (Box 162, Folder 3)
    - Student Papers, n.d. (Box 162, Folder 4)
    - Student Papers, 1993 (Box 162, Folder 5)
    - Student Papers, 1992 (Box 162, Folder 6)
    - Student Papers, 1991-1993 (Box 162, Folder 7)
    - Student Papers, 1964 (Box 162, Folder 8)
    - Student Papers, n.d. (Box 162, Folder 9)
    - Student Papers, n.d. (Box 162, Folder 10)
    - Student Papers, n.d. (Box 162, Folder 11)
    - Student Papers, n.d. (Box 162, Folder 12)
    - Student Papers, 1978 (Box 163, Folder 1)
    - Student Papers, n.d. (Box 163, Folder 2)
    - Student Papers, 1978 (Box 163, Folder 3)
    - Student Papers, 1972 (Box 163, Folder 4)
    - Student Papers, n.d. (Box 163, Folder 5)
    - Student Papers, 1976 (Box 163, Folder 6)
    - Student Papers, 1978 (Box 163, Folder 7)
    - Student Papers, 1997 (Box 163, Folder 8)
    - Student Papers, 1997 (Box 163, Folder 9)
    - Student Papers, 1997 (Box 163, Folder 10)
    - Student Papers, 1996 (Box 163, Folder 11)
    - Student Papers, n.d. (Box 163, Folder 12)
    - Student Papers, 1992 (Box 163, Folder 13)
    - Student Papers, 1992 (Box 163, Folder 14)
    - Student Papers, 1989-1990 (Box 163, Folder 15)
    - Student Papers, n.d. (Box 163, Folder 16)
    - Student Papers, 1981 (Box 163, Folder 17)
    - Student Papers, n.d. (Box 164, Folder 1)
    - Student Papers, n.d. (Box 164, Folder 2)
    - Student Papers, 1981 (Box 164, Folder 3)
    - Student Papers, 1975 (Box 164, Folder 4)
    - Student Papers, 1975 (Box 164, Folder 5)
    - Student Papers, 1975 (Box 164, Folder 6)
    - Student Papers, 1975 (Box 164, Folder 7)
    - Student Papers, 1968-1976 (Box 164, Folder 8)
    - Student Papers, 1970 (Box 164, Folder 9)
    - Student Papers, 1958 (Box 164, Folder 10)
    - Student Papers, 1952-1953 (Box 164, Folder 11)
    - Student Papers, 1966 (Box 164, Folder 12)
    - Student Papers, 1974 (Box 164, Folder 13)
    - Student Papers, 1955 (Box 164, Folder 14)
    - Student Papers, 1974 (Box 164, Folder 15)
    - Student Papers, 1975 (Box 164, Folder 16)
    - Student Papers, 1965-1967 (Box 165, Folder 1)
    - Student Papers, 1976-1979 (Box 165, Folder 2)
    - Student Papers, 1959 (Box 165, Folder 3)
    - Student Papers, n.d. (Box 165, Folder 4)
    - Student Papers, 1952-1953 (Box 165, Folder 5)
    - Recommendations A-B, 1981-1998 (Box 165, Folder 6)
    - Recommendations A-B, 1981-1998 (Box 165, Folder 7)
    - Recommendations C, 1980-1998 (Box 165, Folder 8)
    - Recommendations C, 1981-1998 (Box 165, Folder 9)
    - Recommendations D, 1978-1994 (Box 166, Folder 1)
    - Recommendations E-F, 1981-1996 (Box 166, Folder 2)
    - Recommendations G-H, 1975-1998 (Box 166, Folder 3)
    - Recommendations I-K, 1980-1996 (Box 166, Folder 4)
    - Recommendations L-M, 1975-1997 (Box 166, Folder 5)
    - Recommendations P-R, 1980-1995 (Box 166, Folder 6)
    - Recommendations S, 1981-1998 (Box 166, Folder 7)
    - Recommendations T, 1982-1996 (Box 166, Folder 8)
    - Recommendations U-Z, 1978-1999 (Box 166, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence A, 1988 (Box 167, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence A, n.d. (Box 167, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence A, 1973-1978 (Box 167, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence A, 1986-1987 (Box 167, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence B, 1977-1980 (Box 167, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence B, 1976-1982 (Box 167, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence B, 1969-1981 (Box 167, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence B, 1977-1998 (Box 167, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence B, 1974-1977 (Box 167, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence B, n.d. (Box 167, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence B, 1980 (Box 167, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence B, 1986 (Box 167, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence B, 1970-1977 (Box 167, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence B, 1970-1976 (Box 167, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence B, 1958-1959 (Box 167, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence C, 1985-1986 (Box 167, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence C, 1975 (Box 167, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence C, 1986-1987 (Box 167, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence C, 1967-1999 (Box 167, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence C, 1988-1991 (Box 167, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence C, 1980-1981 (Box 167, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence C, 1958 (Box 167, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence C, 1970-1997 (Box 167, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence D, 1971-1982 (Box 167, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence D, 1958 (Box 167, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence E, 1951-1955 (Box 168, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence E, 1944-1954 (Box 168, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence E, 1939-1954 (Box 168, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence F, 1956-1959 (Box 168, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence F, 1949-1950 (Box 168, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence F, 1958 (Box 168, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence F, 1955-1957 (Box 168, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence F, 1956-1958 (Box 168, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence F, 1955-1957 (Box 168, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence F, 1956 (Box 168, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence F, 1954-1958 (Box 168, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence F, 1956 (Box 168, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence F, 1957-1959 (Box 168, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence F, 1975-1990 (Box 168, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence F, 1971-1994 (Box 168, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence F, 1985 (Box 169, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence G, 1984-1990 (Box 169, Folder 2)